Okay guys, welcome to another video.
So in this video we will see the CS script and WS script that you say.
So both of the things are, you can see there is a script, alright.
Both of say it's equitable, windows internal, have a lot of that or anything, is used
to execute a vbs file, visual basic file or a JavaScript file instead of the host, okay.
So this is the used by XQ2, sorry, used by Windows to execute script or WS script.exe,
you can execute visual basic script or JavaScript files or any files instead of the nation.
So you can see the same for a CS script.exe, you can see the visual basic script has been
executable, okay, binary used with script in Windows, okay, both are the similar.
So I have created one of the small JavaScript file in the machine, which it's a very, very
simple, okay.
So you can see WS script.echo and your machine has been hacked.
So there is some, it will display the input instead of this, you can use some fileless
malware, like PowerShell or CMD-based malware, since the cryptocurrency can execute
it instead of the nation, basically that the attacker will do it like that.
So this kind of CS script, WS script is used to develop malware, like emote, or you can
see some speeders, like emote, or yeah, a lot of things are there, okay.
So you can deliver what malware by using the WS script and you can you can pure your own.
So let's hit on to the CMD, so that I will execute this file to the WS script.exe and
I will click on the link here, click on the link here, and then I will click on the link
there.
Okay.
So you can create your own VBS or JavaScript-based malware by your own or you can use some
tools, like Amazon, or a lot of frameworks, you can do some research and you can create
your own JavaScript malware.
Uh, VBS script malware, so you can you can get into the machine, okay.
So we'll hop off this video and we'll continue our discussion next video.
See you guys, bye bye.